<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<section id="2765">
  <number>0</number>
  <name></name>
  <summary>&lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="@@PLUGINFILE@@/Picture1.png" alt="Advance IET logo" width="450" height="170" class="img-responsive atto_image_button_right"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course and the accompanying materials were developed for the ADVANCE IET project.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/federal-initiatives/iet-toolkit" target="_blank"&gt;ADVANCE IET project&lt;/a&gt; (2022-2025) provides new training opportunities and resources to assist state adult education offices, professional development providers, and local
    program staff in expanding IET programs for adult education participants.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ADVANCE IET project is being conducted by the American Institutes of Research in partnership with World Education, Inc. under contract to the U.S. Department of Education. The project started in September 2022. For more information visit the &lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/federal-initiatives/iet-toolkit" target="_blank"&gt;ADVANCE IET website&lt;/a&gt; or contact &lt;a href="mailto:IETDesignCampInfo@air.org" target="_blank"&gt;IETDesignCampInfo@air.org&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;The ADVANCE Integrated Education and Training (IET): IET Fundamentals course introduces the foundational concepts, requirements, and core elements of IET design and implementation. This is a self-paced course that is designed to take approximately two hours to complete.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;To receive a certificate of completion, participants must score a minimum of 80 percent on a 10-question knowledge check at the end of the course.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;The primary audience for this course is adult education administrators, adult education and workforce training instructors, and career navigators who are unfamiliar with the definition and core design features of IET and the resources available to plan and implement an IET program. The course can also serve as an orientation for new adult education and partner agency staff joining an existing IET team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;A secondary audience is prospective partners from workforce development, occupational training, and industry who are unfamiliar with IET concepts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Course Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Eighty percent of jobs in our economy require some form of postsecondary education and training, but not a four-year degree.&lt;sup&gt;1&lt;/sup&gt; But just 43% of American workers can access training to attain the skills needed for these jobs.&lt;sup&gt;2&lt;/sup&gt; In order to help adults thrive in our economy, which increasingly requires a skilled workforce that can adapt to ever-evolving technology and industry sectors, adult educators understand that adult learners need opportunities to obtain workplace and career readiness skills through career training that prepare them for the complex future they face.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Integrated Education and Training (IET) programs are designed to help adults improve their basic skills while learning occupational and workplace skills to prepare them for in-demand careers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;This course is the first in a series of courses that will be developed through the ADVANCE IET project to provide technical assistance to expand the availability of IET and the quality of IET programs to support diverse adult learner pathways to high-quality careers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Course Objectives&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After completing this course, you will be able to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Explain the rationale for, and benefits of, IET from the perspective of adult learners, employers, and adult education program providers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Describe the core design features of an IET program.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Use program profiles to identify and evaluate core design features implemented in diverse program contexts.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Identify the roles and expertise that each team member (internal adult education team and external partners) contributes to implementing an effective IET.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Locate available resources for in-depth planning and development of an IET.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Course Structure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This course is composed of the following units:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Introduction (5 minutes)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Unit 1: An Introduction to Integrated Education and Training Fundamentals (30 minutes)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Unit 2: Digging Deeper Into IET Program Design Elements (30 minutes)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Unit 3: Getting Started: Resources for IET Planning and Design (40 minutes)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Conclusion (15 minutes)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is the main course page. Some units of the course below include activities, reflections, videos, and other materials to enhance your learning experience. All links open in this window unless otherwise specified.&amp;nbsp;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Most checkboxes will automatically be checked to indicate completion upon viewing the activity, except for the Unit 1 application activity and the final assessment, which are graded and marked complete only after the minimum score for each is achieved.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;Disclaimer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This course was developed under contract with the American Institutes for Research (AIR) with funding from the U.S. Department of Education (ED), Office of Career, Technical, and Adult Education (OCTAE), under Contract No. GS-00F-347CA. The content and
    opinions expressed herein do not necessarily represent the positions or policies of the U.S. Department of Education, and no official endorsement by the U.S. Department of Education should be inferred.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The course may contain resources by a third party outside of the Department of Education. As such, the Department is not responsible for its content, nor can it guarantee it is accessible in accordance with Section 508 of the Rehabilitation Act of 1973.
    If you need access to an accessible version, please reach out to the third-party vendor for assistance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span style=""&gt;Footnote Citations:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;Brown, Katie. Strengthening career pathways for working students: Gateway to Careers Act will help students overcome barriers to postsecondary education. National Skills Coalition. (April 2019). &lt;a href="https://nationalskillscoalition.org/blog/higher-education/strengthening-career-pathways-for-working-students-gateway-to-careers-act-will-help-students-overcome-barriers-to-postsecondary-education/"&gt;https://nationalskillscoalition.org/blog/higher-education/strengthening-career-pathways-for-working-students-gateway-to-careers-act-will-help-students-overcome-barriers-to-postsecondary-education/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;
        &lt;p&gt;The Skills Mismatch," National Skills Coalition. &lt;a href="https://nationalskillscoalition.org/skills-mismatch/"&gt;https://nationalskillscoalition.org/skills-mismatch/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;sub&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To begin, select Unit 1 below.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;</summary>
  <summaryformat>1</summaryformat>
  <sequence>10147</sequence>
  <visible>1</visible>
  <availabilityjson>{"op":"&amp;","c":[],"showc":[]}</availabilityjson>
  <timemodified>1702848472</timemodified>
</section>