<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<activity id="2668" moduleid="10140" modulename="page" contextid="67980">
  <page id="2668">
    <name>Resources</name>
    <intro></intro>
    <introformat>1</introformat>
    <content>&lt;p dir="ltr" style="text-align: left;"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You have explored the IET Toolkit content
and structure and have become familiar with the phases of IET design. We will
end the course with an overview of some of the other resources available to
support IET planning and implementation.&amp;nbsp;After you finish reviewing the resources, return to the main course page to review the &lt;a href="$@PAGEVIEWBYID*10141@$"&gt;Unit Summary.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/professional-development/resource-collections/profile-8850" target="_blank"&gt;Interactive version
of the IET Design Toolkit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In
this module, you explored the PDF version of the IET Design Toolkit.&amp;nbsp; An interactive version is available through
the LINCS Learning Portal, that you logged into in order to access this IET
Fundamentals Course. The content of the interactive version is identical to the
PDF content, but it offers hyperlinks to supplementary websites and provides
downloadable Word versions of the tools and templates.&amp;nbsp;Scroll down the IET Design Toolkit landing page to the section called "Abstract" to find the url to the Interactive version.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/state-resources/federal-initiatives/iet-toolkit/training" target="_blank"&gt;IET
Design Train the Trainer Resources&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This is a comprehensive set of
professional development resources developed for the Basic Design&amp;nbsp;Camps
from the Increasing IET Opportunities for Adults Project (2019 -2022). They
include an IET Design&amp;nbsp;Camp Training Guide, PowerPoint presentations, and
handouts that can be used and customized for&amp;nbsp;local and state professional
development purposes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/state-resources/federal-initiatives/advance-iet" target="_blank"&gt;Resources from
ADVANCE IET&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The ADVANCE IET project builds on the
increasing IET Opportunities for Adult Project and will provide&amp;nbsp;states and
programs with training and technical assistance to develop, strengthen, and
scale IET&amp;nbsp;programs that effectively support diverse adult learner pathways
to high-quality careers. Check this&amp;nbsp;webpage for newly developed resources
from ADVANCE IET, such as:&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;IET
Quality Indicators, a tool for supporting program development and continuous
improvement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;IET
Repository of freely available resources that support IET planning, design,
and&amp;nbsp;implementation.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Online
professional development courses (this course is the first in a series of
three).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Summaries
of specialized IET models.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;…and
more!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/professional-development/resource-collections/profile-1029" target="_blank"&gt;Integrated
Education and Training: Implementing Programs in Diverse Contexts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This
publication features eight examples of IET programs from which practitioners
can draw ideas and inspiration. It was intentionally developed with an emphasis
on “diverse contexts” to offer profiles of IET programs in rural and urban
areas, of varied sizes,&amp;nbsp; implemented in
both community-based organizations and community college settings. Units 1 and
2 of this course draw on some of the profiles in this report. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/professional-development/resource-collections/profile-9076" target="_blank"&gt;Integrated
Education and Training (IET) in Corrections: A Companion Guide to&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/professional-development/resource-collections/profile-9076" style="background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255); font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;the
IET Design Toolkit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style="font-size: 1.7rem;"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This guide summarizes lessons learned
from the IET in Corrections project and serves as a&amp;nbsp;companion to the IET
Design Toolkit. It offers considerations, tools, and examples
for&amp;nbsp;planning, designing, implementing, and evaluating IET programs in prisons
and jails,&amp;nbsp;designed to supplement the guidance provided in the Toolkit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://lincs.ed.gov/professional-development/resource-collections/profile-8808" target="_blank"&gt;Compendium
of Innovative Practices: Adult Education Bridge Programs and Integrated
Education and Training (IET) Programs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;This publication features profiles of
five adult education programs that are implementing Bridge and
IET&amp;nbsp;programs. Bridge programs, according to the compendium are distinct
from IET programs in that they do&amp;nbsp;not include an occupational training component.
Rather, the intention is to allow learners to enroll in&amp;nbsp;postsecondary
education and training upon completion of the Bridge.&amp;nbsp; Both the Bridge and
IET programs&amp;nbsp;featured in the compendium implement common practices, such
as partnerships with local employers&amp;nbsp;and workforce development agencies,
workforce preparation, and contextualized basic skills instruction.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Return to the main course page to review the &lt;a href="$@PAGEVIEWBYID*10141@$"&gt;Unit Summary.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <contentformat>1</contentformat>
    <legacyfiles>0</legacyfiles>
    <legacyfileslast>$@NULL@$</legacyfileslast>
    <display>5</display>
    <displayoptions>a:3:{s:12:"printheading";s:1:"1";s:10:"printintro";s:1:"0";s:17:"printlastmodified";s:1:"1";}</displayoptions>
    <revision>10</revision>
    <timemodified>1702732421</timemodified>
  </page>
</activity>